Don't even think about touching him
It's mine
I'm not scared of any of you
Why?
The really scary thing is
It's behind me now
Gyeonwoo
The back of my head will be pierced
Hey there
Mr. Sangju
Just a moment
Ah...
yes
Oh, I'm nervous.
I did something really naughty
Wouldn’t it be unfair if the back of your head got pierced?
You're protecting yourself without even knowing it
Grandma, your grandson is like that.
Let's chase away bad luck
I'll make you pay it all back with love
I guess you bought something quite wrong.
How can there be so few people?
Hey, the meal is
The default is 30 servings.
Well, well, if that happens...
Is 19 too few?
No matter how many people come
You have to pay for 30 people.
Yes...
Enjoy your meal
This is my first funeral too.
What should I do in times like this?
I can't connect
To voicemail...
What kind of phone call are you making like this?
Not my mother
Someone who can call...
Write it
Jaeil Funeral Home General Room Oh Ok-sun
Come when the time comes
Gyeonwoo’s grandmother passed away
Even though the energy is dirty
Isn't it enough to break the sun?
Isn't your bank account too overflowing?
Even if there was a murder?
Only the people who died in this house
There are three, three
When other towns are going up with the sound of billions and billions
Why isn't this town budging?
we really
I only believe in General Dongcheon.
Don't worry, I'm good.
Are you ready?
Let's go
Light the fire, let's begin
yes
Huh? mom!
Mom, mom, mom, mom!
Mom, what is this!
Ah, selling all that property
What is this, being so penniless, mom?
Let’s at least bring some flowers
Just a photo like that, really.
armband
Ah...
If you go to the entrance office
- I'll bring it to you right away.
- Ask me for yours.
Why? Are you going to stay in Sangju?
Oppa is really funny, huh?
Now they say that
What changes?
If you were going to kick me out
I should have kicked him out last night, huh?
I!
When I said let’s kick him out, overseas or anywhere else!
Mom's remaining assets
Before you mess with him!
you man
Don’t you remember that you passed behind your mother?
therefore!
Still, how should I have convinced him!
You are the eldest son, you are the eldest son!
Uh, uh, baby!
Ah, brother!
Oh, please, you two, calm down.
What are you doing?
Don't you give it to me?
Uh, huh?
Don't touch him, cheat!
I'm sorry, uncle, I just...
Can't you just let me stay here?
Who is your uncle?
This bastard is real!
What are you doing!
- In front of the deceased
- What?
This is the deceased who has been taken care of so far.
Why are you chasing him?
Do you advertise that you are from a soybean flour family?
If you shout loudly
You think everything is true, right?
Are you a shaman?
yes
-Why?
- Shaman?
A shaman at a funeral?
Don’t you know that shamans can’t come to funerals?
As soon as you leave, you'll be treated like a ghost!
You called me, you fraudster?
Oh, that's not it
Come join me!
Until the last road
Are you getting dirty like this?
- Oh, yes, today is today.
- Ghosts are worth a try.
People are difficult
Follow me, follow me
Huh? Don't do it!
surname
Isn't this a bit strange?
Dongcheon!
ghost ears
It's 8 years old!
Get out now!
Get out quickly!
I'm not going out!
Oh my, are you here?
What happened?
Just say thank you
It's the perfect time to say that
thank you
But how did you find out?
Ah, Seongah
Seongah?
Park Seong-ah?
Ah, that's it...
His part-time job is around here.
- Oh, I guess you saw it.
- Ah...
Just in case, go check it out.
Is your part-time job coming to an end soon?
Change your clothes and join naturally
No clothes
Uh, hey, Gyeonwoo.
your parents
They say you'll be arriving soon
I'll go, don't worry.
Do you want to?
thank you
Store, really?
Yeah
Going
Okay, go, go and get some rest.
The face speaks volumes.
You're not catching it?
I thought I'd catch it
That guy just said that
thank you
That's what Gyeonwoo heard today.
It was the only good thing to say
Then you can't catch it
Earlier
If I wasn't a shaman
You wouldn't have suffered that much, right?
Did you get hit?
Because we are still so small
Shaman, can you go home alone?
- Yes
- See you tomorrow then.
Oh, is it okay if I return the good price?
I am confident!
Well, it was before I got older.
So far, only three have died.
Even ghosts die, over there
Well, the excuse is
On the topic of pure quackery
Hey
Don't call another shaman just to get rid of a ghost.
If there's a guy who says he'll take that off,
He's a real quack
Now, good price
No...
What if the exorcism doesn’t work, now?
As long as you hide your life
They are not usually strong demons.
Until I moved to another location myself.
There is nothing a person can do
I can only pray
shake off the darkness
let go of evil
I have no choice but to pray
Guys, are you all done?
First of all, don’t let anyone get near you
Because we’re trying to find a way too
yes
Come on, let's go.
Let's go
Hello?
hello
- Goodbye
- Yes
It's a shame
It's a new bike
Huh? What does this mean?
Didn't someone buy it?
The kid got hit!
I think the kid got run over!
Please call an ambulance
- Didn’t it happen in an accident?
- What should I do?
That's enough
Now go
Okay then, here we go.
Why?
uh?
It's nothing
I heard your grandmother passed away?
Have you finally gotten away from me?
congratulations
to my mother
I know you wrote a fake amulet, right?
Since I won't come, just 100 amulets
No, just write 50 more.
Oh my, are you a brat?
Oh please
I can't write any more
Instead I just shot a link, check it out
What is this?
Special lecture on amulets
I opened an online lecture.
50 per month, if you pay for 12 months all at once
10% DC goes into 540
Are you a scoundrel?
Oh my, oh my, oh my
Would you please say commercial?
But boy
Aren’t you General Dongcheon’s new daughter?
Don’t you know that your new mom’s shoes aren’t ordinary shoes?
I wish you could have faith under him too
Isn't this something you normally wear?
Why did the tiger cub come to the fox?
Damn it, damn it!
Don't call me again, bye bye
Gyeonwoo, I’m sorry.
I'm sorry for making you upset
my grandson
I'm suffering from so much misfortune.
Please save my grandson, okay?
Mom, what is this!
Mom, what the hell is this?
If you were going to kick me out, you should have kicked me out in the evening.
Mom's remaining assets
Before you mess with him!
I'm sorry
Because I'm my grandmother's misfortune...
Are you okay with getting hit earlier?
It stings
It just brought me to my senses.
You are strong.
What kind of crazy bitch...
I am trying to increase my demonic power.
Offered as a living sacrifice?
That kind of witchcraft
I wrote it without fear and fell asleep.
To search
I cut my hair like a three-tiered pile and pulled out my fingernails.
By writing a mantra in blood
I will become a shaman who worships evil spirits.
Don't fall into hell with you, devil.
a promise spell
Whoever wrote it is already not the person
It's a ghost wearing a human shell.
Mother is too much
How could you chew my phone?
What are you doing? It’s pitch dark with all the lights off.
Huh? King’s mother?
When you see an adult
I should start by saying ‘Hello’
Where did you learn this habit?
hello?
Hello, hello
I sent SOS
Do you know how much it hit?
Ta ta ta ta ta ta ta ta!
Mr...
Was it just you?
I was like that too, this one
Don't lie
What kind of thing is your mother?
People must have been talking to my mother!
I won't lose a word
Are you two still on good terms?
It's nothing to laugh at, Mother Wang.
I'm in a complete crisis right now.
Oh my
Not just a crisis, but a major crisis?
yes
It's my first love
Why is that Gyeonwoo’s fault?
It's all bad luck's fault
But you have to survive 37 days safely.
To those mean people
Either accept the apology or fight back.
What's the point if I die before then?
You break bad luck and become just like everyone else, right?
I don’t get hate on Gyeonwoo.
No! You will be very happy?
Because he’s a really, really good kid.
mother
king's mother
please help me
To protect Gyeonwoo
My skills are still very poor.
Mother Wang, I
I'm on my knees, on my knees
Hey, Inseok
Does that mean you kneel down suddenly?
What should I do, then?
I don't even know how
Do you like it a lot?
I love you
What is precious
I protect it with my own hands and make it a habit
The weak lose in the end
'A port to surrender'
'The devil'
‘Mysterious Rain’
‘Written’
Anti-paralysis secretary, a mysterious book that makes the devil surrender
It took 30 minutes to read four letters?
It will take me 10 years to read all of this book.
Kid! When are you going to read all of this?
Hey, Park Seong-ah
Did I eat something wrong?
Why study?
Can you speak Chinese characters?
I can barely read Korean
What is it?
What is this antique?
With a very strong ghost
So that you can win even if you go head to head
It makes you into a scary, strong shaman.
Is it a book with secrets?
Here's Gyeonwoo
How to make sure you keep it
They say it's here somewhere...
It's too difficult
I have no idea what you're talking about
Let's find another way, my friend.
Gyeonwoo won’t be able to come to school today, right?
Yeah, wouldn't it be better to be alone?
That's right
If there's someone next to me
I'm going to be very worried
That's right
Oh, what a surprise!
Hey, good body friend.
Let me ask you one favor.
You don’t like it?
I am an archery coach
Arm strength is no joke
It's just the right time to be alone
There shouldn't be anyone next to you
Uh, no way.
So
Did you leave something behind?
Yeah, I'll just find it and come out soon.
Now, now, now, wait a minute
There is, I'll get it.
no
It’s a secret item only for women.
That...
What about rice?
Have you eaten?
If you haven't eaten yet, would you like to eat together?
I eat really well
my mother said
If only I had the strength to lift a spoon
They say rice goes down your throat
They say that's how life is
I saw you at the funeral
You didn’t even drink a sip of water.
Did you eat anything after that?
funeral service?
Did you come to the funeral?
Didn't you see it?
Ah...
That...
Jiho
I heard it from Jiho.
How could I have gotten there?
I was never there
Ah, that...
So what about that rice?
I wash rice really well.
Would you like to see something?
no, it's okay
Hey, when you actually look at it,
Will you change your mind? It will change completely?
I won't change it
Just take a look
Oh, if you can't find what you're looking for
Please get out quickly
Hey Gyeonwoo
Gyeonwoo, don’t think like that.
What are you thinking?
bad idea
I want to die
That ghost
Only come to that kind of person
Grandma must be sad.
If I see you doing this
Will you please go out?
Hey, Park Seong-ah
What are you doing Park Seong?
Seongah, did you come?
It's nothing
Why you?
The key to the archery club, the coach told me to give it to you.
I delivered, here I go.
chloride contact point
Huh?
Oh, why do you have this?
Contact information, phone number
I don't know
You’re a regular! Why don't you know the number!
I don't know!
Oh my, really
What the hell is this?
Well, really, huh?
The incredibly famous...
Influenza, huh? Okay, that's it, uh
This is the first time a shaman has become this famous.
Because he is so famous, his number is private.
Hey, if you send me a DM for this, I will contact you.
Send it to me?
That's it
Don't sell anything to Yeomhwa.
Take my sin
Thank you for your hard work
I watched it for 10 years!
No, Dong-cheon said we will meet soon?
huh? Why are you hiding?
Just meet each other after seeing each other.
Today
It's not pretty.
It's so pretty that I have to surprise you.
If you wear this at least
It's kind of pretty, huh?
how is it?
mother!
He's giving that damn knee too, why, again?
Oh, please help me.
I don't have time
You...
- You said that was a foul.
- Suicide Ears
Gyeonwoo has a suicidal spirit.
I guess it’s been a while since I brought it home.
I'm not following you yet
I earned a day or two
Don't lose your mind though
Suicide ears are quiet and fast
If we get as close as Oshi's shadow,
I'm going to die, I'm going to kill myself
Oh my, that damn first love
It's difficult too
Do you want to save it like that?
yes
He says he has a reason to live?
Are you a suicidal demon?
Wanting to live comes first
It's not okay to want to save someone else's life.
You may not know what kind of life you want to live in.
If you're so sad
From that point on, you don’t know.
You have to start with wanting to live
Can you do it?
Yeah, I'll try it, whatever.
I have nothing to give but this
Oh my, thank you
Looking at the folk painting frames
My mother-in-law’s luxurious taste is
Where have you gone?
Well, what brought you here?
ah!
That's it
This
My brother or my wife
There wasn't a single photo of my mother-in-law.
I need something to put in the charnel house.
Okay, there are a lot here.
Thank you, uncle.
What is an amulet?
Originally, it was nothing special
Isn’t it a piece of paper?
But he's with another piece of crap
What else?
The amulet contains my heart
The desire to protect someone
I hope you are safe
I hope everything goes well
The heart shakes off bad luck
It's about protecting people.
Ah...
If people go instead of paper
What happens?
A person?
People are strong
It's warm, right?
human amulet
This is how a person becomes a talisman
Instead of paper, engrave words on your body
Stick next to him
If we divide the body temperature like this
Bad luck runs away
That...
Hold hands?
You don't have to hold on to anything
You can just pass by
It's important to share this body temperature
mother
Why?
Ah, ah, ah, first love?
Why, like this
Do, do, do this, do this a little bit
Are you embarrassed?
It's the best way, Mom.
Ouch, ooh, ooh
Fighting
Ah, something like a human talisman.
Why did you tell me now?
I will definitely save Gyeonwoo with my skinship.
Hey Gyeonwoo
Hey Gyeonwoo!
It's been so long
Hey, nice to meet you?
Do you want me to read your palm?
I'm really good at reading palms.
Oh, what should I do?
Should I use my childhood innocence?
hi?
Write...
Ah...
hello
Huh? Too close?
Mistress, Mr. Lee
Have you eaten?
Did you sleep well?
Gyeonwoo, here
Why?
Now
Sloppy?
Ah, Pyoho Good morning
Did you study yesterday?
Is it in very bad condition?
What are you doing?
uh?
Ah, well, now
Which finger is this?
Guess what
- This
- Ding
This
Uh...
You don't see things like that in the morning.
Huh?
Uh, why did you film it with this?
Oh, guys, you're wrong.
This...
It's concentric
Ugh, crap
So, I take a good look
You told me to spread rumors, right?
I mean, ugh.
I too am a victim of fake news
This is typical
It can be seen as a harmful effect of the media.
What atmosphere?
Why is he like this?
Because of him, our Gyeonwooman
I almost got falsely accused for no reason.
What did the arsonist really mean?
I taught math yesterday
I went to ask something.
What?
firebug?
No, I believe in such nonsense.
Get this excuse from the kid!
No, that's not it, Coach Yang.
Inside and out, man
Gyeonwoo, why did he start the fire? uh?
Why did he set fire to the warehouse, you man!
All he set on fire was
Women only have hearts!
Of course, I was a little upset too!
In the end, the homeroom teacher
I apologized to the archery coach.
That's right, I usually
I told you to watch your mouth, right?
Hey, was it just me that was wrong?
You guys also started the rumor together!
You're not careful with your mouth again, really?
I won't do it, I won't!
No...
Because of that, Gyeonwoo can’t even go to school.
Because I'm so sorry
Rather, I can't speak well.
The reason I couldn’t go to school
It's not because of you
Gyeonwoo’s grandmother passed away
That's why I couldn't come out for a few days
Hey, you just fuck the head.
- Wow!
hey!
- I should have been careful.
- Hit me, hit me!
fish oil
Good
I'm glad the misunderstanding was resolved
Huh?
Hit it one more time, harder
Well done
let me help you
Huh?
I'll do it, why...
- Huh?
- Hey, hey.
Hey Gyeonwoo
Where have you been?
Why is there so much dust on my clothes?
- Look at the dust.
- What...
I'm sorry
Oh my, thank you
For picking it up
What are you doing to Gyeonwoo?
A new kind of bullying?
Isn't it?
You, huh?
Who wants to do this all the time?
You didn't do this?
I know
I did this
I'm not harassing you
There are many ways
Use a person as a talisman
So the skinship I do is
Simply to satisfy my self-interest
That's not to say
A heart that only wants to save Gyeonwoo
I willingly sacrifice my whole body with this one heart
It's part of the art of bowing.
There's nothing dark about it
Stop it
Looks very dark
Yeah?
Does it really have to be that hard?
Can't you just reveal everything and say you'll help?
Yeah, you saw it too.
I am a shaman
How difficult is Gyeonwoo?
If you want my help, you have to trust me.
A shaman at a funeral?
Until the last road
Is it polluted like this?
How can I see Gyeonwoo here?
Get in more trouble, huh?
So
Are you just going to be a weirdo?
Yeah
Even if I can't make you understand, I can protect you
If I have no choice but to be hated, I will be hated.
I'll do what I can now, just
Hey
You are so
It looks real
Hey
I'm real
You're a real shaman, you son of a bitch.
Huh?
- What are you doing?
- uh?
uh?
- How long are you going to chase me?
- uh?
Ah, that...
Until it doesn't take?
Did you catch it just now?
Um...
Ah, but
It's the opposite direction from your house.
I'm not going home
Where are you going?
charnel house
Hey Gyeonwoo
There's a grandmother
I guess you had a lot of competitive spirit.
You never smile with a bouquet of flowers
You will only smile if you hang a gold medal around your neck.
I'm a total gold medal hunter.
You can do it well, right?
I need to eat something delicious
I have to beat my friends
rock paper scissors
congratulations
thank you
grandmother
It was good back then
That was good
Thank goodness
When did this...
Now, this performance evaluation is
Life and ethics Among the topics of each unit
pick one
awareness raising campaign program
I'm going to make it
It's all the same
Okay, I'll give you 10 minutes from now on.
Each person picks a leader
In most cases, PPT presenters
Get it out in advance, so we don't fight.
I'll be the leader
Isn’t there anyone dissatisfied?
There is no
I'm already sitting in the leader's seat.
- Hey
- Huh?
you are encouraging
Me?
You are the co-pilot
There's no need to be a co-pilot
Do you just want to do it or do you want to do it right?
I just want to do it
Just do it, okay?
It's ruined, completely
Fucked, completely
Doyeonah
why are you so ugly
Are you wearing it on your body?
Our Gyeonwoo is dangerous
Okay, then you do it.
Three bad gods
There are three types of ghosts to avoid
Laughing ghost, dancing ghost, baby ghost
What do you think they have in common?
Do you play well alone?
It's roughly correct, but exactly
Those three aren't complaining
Usually other ghosts
If you comfort me, they will leave.
They're not, they don't make sense
We have to communicate through these words to have a conversation
need to talk
I'll let you go, won't you?
Then the baby ghost
It must be the most painful, right?
You don't know what to say at all.
That's right
The most ugly of the three, this one
Even just one suicide attempt would kill me.
A baby spirit
Well, then what should I do?
you wait a moment
I'm sorry
Why is it like that
Jiho, let’s collect data with me.
Cowherd friend!
Did you come to that archery range?
It's just, whatever.
How are you feeling after shooting that bow for the first time in a while?
It feels great in your hand, right?
Are you starting archery again?
no, no
But this friend
If you shoot a bow
Let’s get things organized and go!
Who, man, would leave something like that?
- It's all sorted...
- Follow me, man.
Clean it up and go
Follow me right now
- No...
- Follow me.
Every corner, huh?
There, down there too
Hey Gyeonwoo
Isn’t this archery really great?
huh?
Oh, I'm not telling you to do anything.
Tsk, that...
There is a teacher
Ever since I was young
Have you been dumped by women a lot?
I don't understand
Well, it continued like that anyway.
But
I hear you say I hate you
Women who are kicked with a single knife
I think about this forever
Ah, then I'll hit back like this
I should at least get back the money I paid for it.
I bought that for 250 at a duty free shop, Mr.
They still appear in my dreams these days
This is something I can't forget
But look what?
you don't like this
We're kind of like this to each other
I don't think it fits well
As I explain it one by one,
The women who took pains to break up with me
Well, I can't remember anything after that.
Ah, that was back then.
There was a kid like that.
um
you
I dated him for 10 years.
Even if we break up
I'm saying break up slowly and painstakingly.
um
That way, no regrets remain
Who is he?
Don’t you know Bae Gyeon-woo?
1st place in high school
I see him doing archery again.
Oh, cool.
good at it
Huh?
You like archery a lot.
Thank goodness
Only for our zodiac signs
I'm telling you specifically
Now, when the baby is born
If it's a hundred, it's a hundred
Everyone writes a self-defense report like this
But does the baby know self-defense?
No, no!
I don't know, this is it
So, am I a self-defense expert?
I don't use it
Write a real assassination order
Baby-ryeong is going to a good place too.
I have to hope for the best so I don't fall
This talisman
You must be able to write with a kind heart.
Like who? like me
Completion of Jinsal Command
I'll put this on Doyeon's desk tomorrow.
Soothe the baby spirit
Pigeon
Suicide devil, just wait for you
- Huh?
- Oh, surprise.
Oh! hi?
You came early, a lot.
Good morning
hello
Are you going to go archery?
no
Hey, I'm going to go archery.
I really like archery
Look at me for a moment
you these days
Don’t you think I’m following you too much?
okay?
Oh, isn't it?
Why do you keep following me?
Don't follow me
I'm not following you around
Wherever I go you are there
You're calling that an excuse now
It doesn't work
I have a question
Can I ask?
uh
I mean archery
How do you feel when you do it? When shooting a bow
That's him, the possessed kid
Yeah, it's all because of him
Didn’t it happen in an accident?
- That's how accidents happen.
- So
- Because of him.
- I bought something today too.
Isn't that right, all of a sudden?
He shoots well
ok
No matter how strong the wind blows
You can win it all with one arrow
It's cool, it's amazing
Why are you following me?
Children are supposed to be protected by adults.
you protect yourself
So I want to be nice to you
Is that okay?
Are you a virgin?
It's friendship
A
When you see it, your mind will change, it will completely change.
Which finger is this?
Guess what
Well done
I'm sorry
- Hey, Bae Gyeon-woo!
- huh?
Let's high five!
- suddenly?
- Uh, suddenly.
- Anyway
- Quick!
uh?
first love
start
Hello, good morning
The weather is nice
I don't do archery, my child
Sweet and sour
Nothing bad will happen in the future
I will defeat them all
Because the three of us are friends
Is this uncomfortable?
Do I feel like I’m the only one being left out?
Let's talk for a moment
What are you talking about?
Because of my part-time job
I think I should go first.
I'll take you there
The guy inside
It's a barrier designed to create an evil spirit.
I found it, it's on my face...
Can you please take this off?